
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " When does the ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException occur?",
    answer: "Run-time",
    options: [
      "Compile-time",
      "Run-time",
      "Not an error",
      "Not an exception at all"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Assuming int is of 4bytes, what is the size of int arr[15];?",
    answer: "60",
    options: [
      "15",
      "19",
      "11",
      "60"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The data structure required to check whether an expression contains a balanced parenthesis is?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Queue",
      "Array",
      "Tree"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The prefix form of A-B/ (C * D ^ E) is?",
    answer: "	150 metres",
    options: [
      "	-/*^ACBDE",
      "	-ABCD*^DE",
      "	-A/B*C^DE",
      "	-A/BC*^DE"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which data structure is used for implementing recursion?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Queue",
      "Stack",
      "Array",
      "List"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The data structure required for Breadth First Traversal on a graph is?",
    answer: "Queue",
    options: [
      "Queue",
      "Array",
      "Stack",
      "Tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A queue follows which principle",
    answer: "FIFO (First In First Out) principle",
    options: [
      "FIFO (First In First Out) principle",
      "LIFO (Last In First Out) principle",
      "Ordered array",
      "Linear tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the time complexity of inserting at the end in dynamic arrays?",
    answer: "Either O(1) or O(n)",
    options: [
      "O(1)",
      "O(n)",
      "Either O(1) or O(n)",
      "O(logn)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "A linear collection of data elements where the linear node is given by means of pointer is called?",
    answer: "Linked list",
    options: [
      "Linked list",
      "Node list",
      "Unordered list",
      "Primitive list"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The concatenation of two lists can be performed in O(1) time. Which of the following variation of the linked list can be used?",
    answer: "Circular doubly linked list",
    options: [
      "Singly linked list",
      "Doubly linked list",
      "Circular doubly linked list",
      "Array implementation of list"
    ]
  }
 

];